amasty.com 2019-01-16

# Privacy Policy | Amasty

Amasty® trademark is operated by a group of companies (referred as Amasty further in this document), which include Amasty Development Limited (Malta), NetStra Solutions s.r.o. (Slovakia) and Design Enterprise Limited (United Kingdom). This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.

## **What information do we collect about you?**

We collect information about you when you register with us or place an order for products or services. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback, subscribe to newsletter and contact us. Website usage information is collected using cookies.

The following information is collected upon placing an order with Amasty: first and last name, e-mail address, billing details, company information such as company name and tax number. We require this information to enter into a binding contract (which is a purchase our products), to issue invoices, credit memos and other legal documents. This information is stored for a legal reasons.

## **How will we use the information about you?**

We collect information about you to process your order, manage your account, and, if you agree, to e-mail you about status of your order, status of your payment, delivery instructions, information about other products and services we think may be of interest to you.

We use your information collected from the website to personalise your repeat visits to our website. If you agree, we shall pass on your personal information to our group of companies so that they may provide you with the purchased services and deliver purchased products.

Amasty will not share your information for marketing purposes with companies outside the group.

In processing your order, we may use information from fraud protection agencies.

## **How long do we store the information?**

We store your personal information (such as name and e-mail address) for as long as you use our extensions or services. This allows you do be able to download free updates and to contact us for support. We store billing details of your company for 10 years as required by tax law, which may be used for audition or other legal purpose.

In case you would like your personal information to be removed, updated or modified, please contact us.

## **Marketing**

We would like to send you information about products and services of ours which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date.

You have right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or using your information for marketing purposes.

| 

## **Access to your information and correction**

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please e-mail us at [support@amasty.com](mailto:support@amasty.com). We provide this information free of charge.

We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate. 

## **Cookies**

Cookies are text files placed on your computer’s browser to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. 

Cookies are also used to handle the same visitor session while you browse between pages of the website.

For further information visit [https://www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/).

You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above website tells you how to remove cookies from your browser. However in some cases some of our website features may not function as a result.

## **Other websites**

Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.

## **Changes to our privacy policy**

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this website page/block. This privacy policy was last updated on 25 of April 2018.

## **How to contact us**

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:

  * \- by e-mail ([support@amasty.com](mailto:support@amasty.com))
  * \- or write us at Amasty Development Ltd, 123 Melita Street, Valletta, VLT 1123, Malta.

Privacy policy last updated on 10th of May, 2018.
